

# BERKAY ÖZTÜRK

**GAME PRODUCER** 

## **PERSONAL**

I am working in game industry for 3 years and worked with teams with multidisciplinary fields. I started as a game developer but improved my game design skills quickly by failing and trying again. My current focus is game design mostly interested in core game mechanics and level design. I am still improving my skills on game art, visual design because creating great experiences require overall understanding of game as a whole.

date of birth 13.10.1996

### CONTACT

Number: +90 (538) 248 2824 Email: bberkayozturk@gmail.com Portfolio: berkaay.github.io/portfolio

## PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

### **Game Producer**

Good Job Games, September 2020- March 2021

- Pitched new game ideas for the product team.
- Produced new game ideas with a studio.
- Lead studio of 5 people consisting of game developers and game artists.
- Lead game design team (3 months)
- Worked with growth team to optimize games for high retention and low CPI.

# **Game Developer**

Good Job Games, January 2020- September 2020

- Developed hypercasual games using Unity engine from ground up.
- Developed tools for level design.
- Pitched game design ideas.

## Game Developer

The Bob Games, November 2018 - January 2020

- Developed hypercasual games using Unity engine from ground up.
- Created necessary game art using Illustrator and Blender.
- Worked with publishers to improve gameplay and design.

# **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

### **Bilkent University**

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, 2014-2018

- Graduated with a GPA of 3.0/4.0
- Chairman of Free Software Society
- Active member of Bilkent Game Developers society.
- Took courses in game design, sound design, visual design.
- Developed a social gaming platform and won "Most Innovative Project" award.

# **MY REFERENCES**

ilker Ilicali, Founder Good Job Games Contact: +90 (535) 022 0189

Bülent Öztürk, Head Of Casual Good Job Games Contact: +90 (532) 357 0240